Matthew Gazzano

BI Analyst

Contact

(973) 461-9100



Mattgazzano@gmail.com



A Lyndhurst, NJ



in Linkedin.com/matthewgazzano

About

BI Analyst with focused experience in reporting and Throughout my current role, results driven environment through coordinating and tracking high profile pharmaceutical point of care campaigns. While working in a startup environment, I have also been able to help develop new processes to optimize campaign objectives through a

Education

Montclair State University

Feliciano School of Business - AACSB Accredited

Master of Science in Business Analytics (MSBA) – Part Time Class of 2022

Ramapo College of New Jersey

Mahwah, NJ

January 2018

Montclair, NJ

Anisfield School of Business - AACSB Accredited

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration: Marketing - 3.6

Experience



Health Monitor Network

Montvale, NJ

Senior Bl Analyst

June 2020 - Present

- Own standardized reporting for C-level management on status of digital product
- Team lead for developing & maintaining querying workspace for all operational data inside Google BigQuery
- Lead CRM design for day-to-day procedures and Ad hoc objectives (Zoho CRM)
- Aid in department implementation of NetSuite ERP

Digital Operations Analyst

January 2018 - June 2020

- Produce weekly dashboards and ad hoc reports on campaign deployment to C-level management. Identify KPI's
- Develop, execute, and maintain standard operating procedures to deliver on sponsor programs across all digital products in network
- Optimize and coordinate the input and output of project deliverable data in CRM database
- Onboard new vendors with current processes and hold them accountable for delivery through tracking performance metrics

Sales & Operations Intern

May 2016 - December 2017

- Responsible to manage the installation and update of digital products- interacted with new and existing clients via phone and email
- Utilized CRM and Job Management software to reconcile field activity reports against work orders
- Verified healthcare providers for eligibility of sale and sponsor targeting
- Assisted sales team with telemarketing efforts when needed

Skills / Applications

Microsoft Excel – Advanced Functions (XLOOKUP, COUNTIFS), Power Query, Power Pivot, Pivot Tables, VBA / Macros

Database Tools – Google BigQuery, MS Access, SQL queries - Joins, Common Table Expressions, Aggregate Functions, Window Functions

Other Applications: CRM - (Zoho CRM), Data Visualization (Microsoft Power BI), Online Forms (Jot Form), Project Management Software (Airtable), Google Sheets & Google Sheets API's

Extracurricular

Published Musician- Can be found on **Spotify**!